randomstreetview.com 2017-04-04

# randomstreetview.com - privacy policy

**Last update: November 1st, 2015**

Welcome to randomstreetview.com.

This privacy policy explains how I use information about you when you use the services provided by me via [http://randomstreetview.com](http://randomstreetview.com/) (the “Service”). 

**Collection of Information**

The Service is designed not to collect any information by itself; no information is stored at randomstreetview.com servers except for standard logging as is usual in webhosting environments. The client-side interactions on the Service make use of third-party services that do collect information, these are covered in the three paragraphs below.

**Google Maps APIs**

The Service uses Google Maps APIs and this privacy policy incorporates the Google Privacy Policy (currently <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>) as amended by Google from time to time.

**Social Sharing Features**

The Service may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button), which let you share actions you take on our Service with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

**Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others**

Third party vendors, including Google, may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Service and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by me and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Service and other websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). 

**Cookies**

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Service. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact me at [feedback@randomstreetview.com](mailto:feedback@randomstreetview.com).
